TV dinner on the golden place.
Late night tweets decide the fate.
Billion dollar bill for another wall.
Rules don't matter if you want it, scumbag.
Sign it fast, don't read the checks.
Who needs a conference when you're on debt?
King with a pen, way better than feel so good to play pretend.
Pay each second a day.
Oh, oh, oh, unlimited play.
Woke up late, grabbed a big mat.
Spilled ketchup all over a diplomatic fact.
Throws the tantrum signs away.
Morphine someone tries to make him obey.
Checks and balances sound like a bore.
Toss the Constitution onto the floor.
Sign it fast, don't read the text.
We'll meet at Congress when you're a dick.
King with a pen, wave it again.
Feels so good to play pretend.
Bae-ae-ae-ae-ae-ae-ae-ae-ae-ae-ae-ae-ae-ae-ae-ae-ae-ae-ae-ae-ae-ae-ae-ae-ae